http://www.anritsu.com/en-AU/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
HomeAnritsu Group Privacy Policy
Anritsu Group Privacy Policy
The Anritsu Corporation and its group companies ("Anritsu"), recognizing its social responsibility to appropriately protect the personal information (information that can be used to identify a specific individual) of all individuals it has connections with, including its customers, shareholders/investors, business partners and employees, has adopted the following privacy policy, and will take all possible measures to ensure the proper handling and protection of personal information in its possession.
Anritsu will strictly comply with all laws, regulations and other social standards concerning the protection of personal information.
Anritsu will strive to properly administer personal information by appointing a person in charge of overall control of personal information and by placing a personal information administrator in each division that handles personal information.
Anritsu will educate its officers, staff and other personnel with regard to protection of personal information.
Anritsu will collect, use and provide personal information in an appropriate manner.
Specifically,
It will collect personal information in an appropriate and fair manner, clearly stating the intended use at the time of collection.
It will not collect "Special care-required personal information", except in cases where advance consent of the person concerned has been received or where permissible by law.
It will use personal information only for the purposes specified by notification or public announcement, or that were made clear at the time of collection, except in cases where advance consent of the person concerned has been received or where permissible by law.
It will not provide personal information to third parties other than group companies or their service providers, except in cases where advance consent of the person concerned has been received or where permissible by law.
In cases where personal information is provided to third parties, or received from third parties, it will keep a record appropriately, except in cases where permissible by law.
In cases where personal information is provided to service providers or others, it will take appropriate measures, in the form of a written contract or otherwise, to ensure that personal information is protected.
Anritsu will respond reasonably and appropriately to confirmation, revision or other requests from individuals regarding their own personal information, upon confirming their identities.
Anritsu will take all reasonable human, physical, technological, and operational measures to ensure that personal information is handled safely and shall make utmost efforts to prevent unauthorized access to, leakage, or loss of personal information.
Anritsu will periodically review this policy and associated company regulations and operating procedures, making revisions and improvements on an ongoing basis.
September 1, 2017
ANRITSU CORPORATION
Handling of Personal Information
Purpose of Utilization
We will utilize your personal information for the following purposes:
To execute customer's contractual obligations;
For the development, improvement, sale, offering, installment, after service, repair, maintenance, marketing and promotion of the products (including systems and software.) relating to company`s business purposes;
To provide useful information of our products (including systems and software.) and services related to the business purposes;
For investors relationship as well as business activities related to our company business;
For management of our shareholders;
For research and study as well as questionnaire of the above purposes;
To respond to inquiries; and
To provide services pertaining to any of the above business purposes.
Furthermore, for efficient business operation, we may provide your personal information to outsource part of the business to a third party. In this case, we will place an agreement with the third party on how to handle your personal information as necessary and appropriate to fully protect your personal information.
Disclosure and providing personal information to a third party
We will not disclose or provide personal data to a third party other than the above outsourcing purpose or unless we meet the following criteria:
Consent from the principal;
In a manner where personal information is not identifiable such as statistical data base;
Requested under laws and regulations;
For the protection of human life, body or fortune and difficult to obtain consent from the principal.
In cases where there is a need to cooperate with the central government organization or a local government, or a person entrusted by them performing affairs prescribed by laws and regulations, and when there is a possibility that obtaining a principal's consent would interfere with the performance of the said affairs; and
For use among the group companies of the individual data.
Shared use of personal information
We may share your personal information within the group companies described below.
Items on shared usage of the personal data
Name of the customer;
Contacts (address, phone number, email address);
Transaction records with our company.
Scope of shared usage of the personal data
Anritsu Group Worldwide
Purposes of usage of the personal data
Development, improvement, sale, offering, installment, after service, repair and maintenance, marketing and sales promotion of Anritsu products (Including system and software) and services relating to our business purposes.
To provide useful information on product (including system and software), service and activity relating to our business purposes.
For research and questionnaire purposes relating to the above services.
Responsibility of handling the personal data
ANRITSU CORPORATION
Disclosure, Correction, Deletion, Termination of usage etc.
Should there be any inquiry on personal information we possess, or request to correct, delete or terminate the usage of the personal information due to error or change, we will confirm that the inquiry is from the said person, and within a timely manner and scope of disclosure, answer to the inquiry, correct or delete etc. such personal information.
Please be noted that deletion or termination of usage of part or entire personal information may hinder us from providing you satisfying services. (We may not be able to delete or terminate usage of those information we possess under certain law requirements.)
Contact Information
Please use the inquiry form (Contact Us) for any inquiries on your personal information or any questions regarding the Privacy Policy.
As a general rule, answer to inquiry will be in writing. For certain information, we may ask you to fill out our form. In these circumstances, we will send you those forms, so please kindly fill them out and send it back to us.
About this website
Usage of Cookies
Within some of the pages of our website, we use a technology called "Cookies" to enhance the experience of our website when you re-visit. "Cookies" is an industry standard technology which the server recognizes your computer. "Cookies" recognizes your computer, but unless you type in your personal information you will not be identified. Furthermore, depending on the type of your browser, you may choose to disable the cookies. As a consequence, there may be some cases where you may not be able to use partial or the entire services we provide.
Access log
We may collect your IP address and domain name within our Web server to analyze site access when you visit our website. These information will be deleted as necessary after the report is created.
The purposes of the Company shall be to engage in the following businesses:
Manufacture and sale of telecommunications equipment and tools;
Manufacture and sale of general electrical equipment and tools;
Manufacture and sale of general equipment and tools;
Manufacture and sale of precision equipment and tools;
Manufacture and sale of medical equipment and tools;
Manufacture and sale of electronic components, microchip, and semiconductor circuit;
Development and sale of system and software associated with the above;
Rental, purchase, recycling, and maintenance service of equipment and tools associated with the above;
Contracting for construction works;
Leasing of real estate;
Services for information and telecommunications, information processing, and information providing;
Worker dispatching services; and
Any and all activities incidental to any of the foregoing items and investment.
Confirm your country below to see local events, contact information and special offers.
